Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 5 and District 5 Locals, 1936-1983 UE.4.1.5
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 5 Locals, 2.
  - Local 512
    - Local 512 Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - L. Harris to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, July 30, 1937; 1.
      - Ross Cain to Frederick Weber Regarding Philco Strike, September 15, 1947; 2.
  - Local 513 (RCA)
    - Local 513 (RCA) Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1947 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Julius Emspak to Irving Burman Regarding Fees, September 16, 1938; 1.
      - Emspak to Burman Regarding Emspak's Availability, October 13, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to Burman Regarding Proposal on Per Capita, October 18, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to Burman Regarding Check, November 28, 1938; 4.
      - Emspak to Burman Regarding Per Capita, March 20, 1939; 5.
      - Emspak to Burman Regarding Status of Local, March 27, 1939; 6.
      - Emspak to Burman Regarding Check, June 22, 1939; 7.
      - Emspak to Marcel Lord Regarding Supplies, February 21, 1940; 8.
      - Emspak to Bernard Tremblay Regarding Charter, November 21, 1947; 9.
      - James Matles to Burman Regarding People's Press and Mailing List, January 13, 1938; 10.
    - Local 513 (RCA) Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Irving Burman to Julius Emspak Regarding Charter, August 16, 1938; 1.
      - Burman to Emspak Regarding Charter, September 7, 1938; 2.
      - Burman to Emspak Regarding Receipts, September 7, 1938; 3.
      - Burman to Emspak Regarding Check and Financial Report, October 9, 1938; 4.
      - Burman to Emspak Regarding Members List, December 20, 1938; 5.
      - Burman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita Reports, February 21, 1939; 6.
      - Burman to Emspak Regarding Financial Situation of Locals, March 25, 1939; 7.
      - Burman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Initiation Payments, July 26, 1939; 8.
      - Marcel Lord to Emspak Regarding Charter, January 19, 1940; 9.
    - Local 513 (RCA) Report of Financial Secretary, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Local 513 (RCA) Organization, 1938-1941 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - C.S. Jackson to James Matles, January 8, 1938; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Jackson, October 13, 1939; 2.
      - Irving Burman to Matles with Wage Rates, April 4, 1939; 3.
      - Matles to Jack Shaw, August 26, 1941; 4.
      - Shaw to Matles, August 28, 1941; 5.
      - Shaw to Matles, September 4, 1941; 6.
      - Matles to Shaw, September 9, 1941; 7.
      - Harry Peace to Matles, October 29, 1941; 8.
      - Matles to Stella, November 4, 1941; 9.
      - Emspak to Peace, November 5, 1941; 10.
  - Local 513 (Lindsey)
    - Local 513 (Lindsey) Organization, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - George Harris to Julius Emspak, September 12, 1944; 1.
      - Emspak to B.M. Stuland, September 20, 1943; 2.
  - Local 513 (Federal Electric)
    - Local 513 (Federal Electric) Officers Lists, November 7, 1947-February 16, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Local 513 (Federal Electric) Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Benard Tremblay, November 21, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Local 513 (Federal Electric) Organization, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Ross Russell to Julius Emspak, November 6, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Russell, November 7, 1947; 2.
      - C.S. Jackson to Emspak, November 7, 1947; 3.
      - George Harris to Emspak, November 17, 1947; 4.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Jackson, November 18, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak to Russell, November 21, 1947; 6.
    - Local 513 (Federal Electric) Disbanding, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to C.S. Jackson, December 12, 1952; 1.
      - Jackson to Fitzgerald with Resolution, December 17, 1952; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Jackson, December 23, 1952; 3.
      - Emspak to Jackson, December 23, 1952; 4.
      - Jean Pare to Emspak, January 6, 1953; 5.
      - Emspak to Pare, January 8, 1953; 6.
  - Local 514
    - Local 514 Incoming Correspondence, 1941-1953, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
      - B. Chase Regarding New Address, n.d.; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Averil Arrowsmith Regarding Supplies, October 14, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Alice Fritsch Regarding UE News, April 20, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to C. Rosen Regarding Per Capita Payments, June 9, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Alexander Horak Regarding Waiver, April 6, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to C. Sullivan Regarding Strike, July 29, 1946; 6.
      - Emspak to W. Moffat Regarding Strike Relief, August 1, 1946; 7.
      - Emspak to John Osborne Regarding Ladies Auxiliaries, August 21, 1946; 8.
      - Joe Spence to Local 514 Regarding Membership Meeting, June 30, 1953; 9.
      - Spence to Local 514 Regarding Membership Meeting, July 4, 1953; 10.
    - Local 514 Outgoing Correspondence, 1942-1952, undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
      - Thelma Bruff to Julius Emspak Regarding Address, July 1, 1942; 1.
      - W. Duff Regarding Supplies, n.d.; 2.
      - Alice Fritsch to Emspak Regarding New Secretary, July 22, 1942; 3.
      - Fritsch to Emspak Regarding Cancellation of UE News Subscription, March 22, 1943; 4.
      - Fritsch to Emspak Regarding Denied Cancellation, n.d.; 5.
      - Alexander Horak to Emspak Regarding Veterans Initiation Stamps, April 3, 1945; 6.
      - W.C. Moffat to James Matles Regarding Strike, n.d.; 7.
      - John Osborne to Emspak Regarding Bonding, May 6, 1949; 8.
      - Osborne to Emspak Regarding Check and Order, August 11, 1950; 9.
      - Osborne to Emspak Regarding Women's Auxiliary, August 14, 1952; 10.
      - C. Rosen to Emspak Regarding Per Capita Payments, June 6, 1944; 11.
      - C.R. Sullivan to Emspak Regarding Strike Report, July 25, 1946; 12.
      - John Wigdor to Emspak Regarding Strike Report, July 25, 1946; 13.
    - Local 514 Coulter Brass Organization, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 76)
      - George Harris to Julius Emspak, September 2, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to H. Peace, September 11, 1941; 2-3.
      - Charter Application, September 15, 1941; 4.
      - Brief History, September 1941; 5.
    - Local 514 Charter Opening, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - George Harris to Julius Emspak, September 13, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Harris, October 11, 1943; 2.
    - Local 514 Ontario Labor Relations Board, 1943-1946 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - D.W. Mather to UE, November 14, 1945; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Mather, November 19, 1945; 2.
      - Mather to Emspak, November 21, 1945; 3.
      - Mather to UE, February 18, 1946; 4.
      - Mather to UE, February 19, 1946; 5.
      - Emspak to Mather, February 21, 1946; 6.
      - Emspak to Mather, February 25, 1946; 7.
      - Mather to UE, April 23, 1946; 8.
      - Emspak to Mather, April 24, 1946; 9.
      - Mather to UE, June 4, 1946; 10-11.
      - Emspak to Mather, June 6, 1946; 12.
      - Mather to UE, July 17, 1946; 13.
      - Emspak to Mather, July 23, 1946; 14.
      - Mather to UE, August 2, 1946; 15.
      - Emspak to Mather, August 5, 1946; 16.
      - Mather to UE, September 23, 1946; 17.
      - Emspak to Mather, September 30, 1946; 18.
    - Local 514 Imperial Optical Strike, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, November 1, 1945; 1.
      - Report of Strike, November 6, 1945; 2.
      - Termination of Strike, December 5, 1945; 3.
    - Local 514 Electro Metallurgical Strike, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - Report of Strike, July 8, 1946; 1.
      - Secretary of Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson, July 29, 1946; 2.
    - Local 514 Canada Wire Strike, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      - Report of Strike, July 9, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson, August 1, 1946; 2.
    - Local 514 IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      - George Harris to Albert Fitzgerald, July 6, 1953; 1.
      - Harris to Local Secretaries, July 6, 1953; 2.
    - Local 514 Correspondence and Report, 1943-1946 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding UE News, March 31, 1943; 1.
      - J.F. Douglas to Emspak Regarding Organization and C.P. Wayman, June 29, 1943; 2.
      - Report of Strike at Amalgamated Electric, July 8, 1946; 3.
    - Local 514 Leaflets, 1953, undated (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Contract, November 27, 1953; 1.
      - "Imperial Optical Strike Settlement", n.d.; 2.
      - "Local 514 Records Progress", n.d.; 3.
      - "The UE Drives Forward", n.d.; 4.
  - Local 515
    - Local 515 Officers Lists, May 16, 1943-February 29, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Local 515 Incoming Correspondence, 1941-1946 (Box 6, Folder 86)
      - Julius Emspak to Local 515 Regarding Supplies, October 20, 1941; 1.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Jerry Wilkie Regarding Receipt of Letter, November 21, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Wilkie Regarding War Production, December 1, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to C. Deeley Regarding Bonding, March 27, 1945; 4.
      - Emspak to W. Blair Regarding Waiver, March 5, 1946; 5.
      - Emspak to Sydney Crocker Regarding Bonding, December 11, 1946; 6.
    - Local 515 Outgoing Correspondence, 1941-1946 (Box 6, Folder 87)
      - W.E. Blair to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, February 27, 1946; 1.
      - Jerry Wilkie to Emspak Regarding Attached Letter, November 18, 1941; 2.
      - Wilkie to Emspak Regarding Data, November 27, 1941; 3.
    - Local 515 Charter Application and Local History, September 1941 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Local 515 The Otis Fensom Organizer Newspaper, March 16, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Local 515 "A Statement for the Information of Employees" Pamphlet, undated (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Local 516
    - Local 516 Officers Lists, February 24, 1943-June 16, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Local 516 Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 92)
      - Julius Emspak to W. Paul Regarding Bonding, February 1, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Tom Mitchell Regarding Supplies, May 1, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Grace Wickham Regarding Waiver, June 27, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Wickham Regarding Audit Report, September 24, 1945; 4.
    - Local 516 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1946 (Box 6, Folder 92)
      - Harry Bell to Julius Emspak Regarding Address, March 30, 1946; 1.
      - T.M. Mitchell Regarding Change In Secretary, September 1944; 2.
      - Mitchell to Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 27, 1945; 3.
      - W. Paul to Emspak Regarding Bonding, January 28, 1943; 4.
      - P. Pawliuk to Emspak Regarding Office Move, January 18, 1944; 5.
      - Grace Wickman to Emspak Regarding Waiver, June 23, 1945; 6.
    - Local 516 Ontario Labor Relations Board, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 93)
      - J.P. Nicol to UE, January 11, 1945; 1.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Nicol, January 13, 1945; 2.
    - Local 516 Miscellaneous, 1942-1947 (Box 6, Folder 94)
      - Charter Application, March 16, 1942; 1.
      - George Harris to Julius Emspak, April 9, 1947; 2.
  - Local 517 (Taylor Electric)
    - Local 517 (Taylor Electric) Organization, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 95)
      - Charter Application, July 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to George Harris, August 3, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to C.S. Jackson, November 17, 1942; 3.
  - Local 517 (Robbins & Myers)
    - Local 517 (Robbins & Myers) Outgoing Correspondence, Alec Grist to Julius Emspak, September 2, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Local 517 (Robbins & Myers) Finances, Bill, July 20, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Local 517 (Robbins & Myers) Organization, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 98)
      - George Harris to Julius Emspak, June 11, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to C.S. Jackson, June 15, 1943; 2.
      - Harris to Emspak, July 5, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Harris, July 13, 1943; 4.
    - Local 517 (Robbins & Myers) Disbanding, George Harris to Julius Emspak, April 10, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Local 517 (Hart Manufacturing)
    - Local 517 (Hart Manufacturing) Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Edna Saigle, January 20, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Local 517 (Hart Manufacturing) Organization, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 101)
      - Ross Russell to Julius Emspak, January 14, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to C.S. Jackson, January 20, 1948; 2.
      - Emspak to Russell, January 20, 1948; 3.
      - George Harris to Emspak, March 23, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Harris, April 2, 1948; 5.
      - Russell to Emspak, April 29, 1948; 6.
  - Local 517 (GE)
    - Local 517 (GE) Officers Lists, April 29, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Local 517 (GE) Correspondence and Memorandum, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 103)
      - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Organization, May 9, 1948; 1.
      - Memo Regarding Disbanding, November 19, 1948; 2.
  - Local 517 (GE Office)
    - Local 517 (GE Office) Organization, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 104)
      - Ross Russell to Julius Emspak, July 13, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to Russell, July 13, 1950; 2.
      - Emspak to Russell, July 18, 1950; 3.
      - Russell to Emspak, August 2, 1950; 4.
  - Local 517 (Welland)
    - Local 517 (Welland) Correspondence, Ross Russell to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, September 6, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Local 518
    - Local 518 Officer Lists, January 4, 1947 - April 7, 1952, undated (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Local 518 Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to H.P. Black Regarding Supplies, January 8, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Local 518 Outgoing Correspondence, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 108)
      - H.P. Black to Julius Emspak Regarding Charter and Supplies, January 4, 1947; 1.
      - R. Durocher to Emspak Regarding Financial Report, May 15, 1947; 2.
    - Local 518 Organization, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 109)
      - Ross Russell to Julius Emspak, November 7, 1946; 1.
      - Russell to Emspak, December 3, 1946; 2.
  - Local 518 (General)
    - Local 518 (General) Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to George Harris, October 23, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Local 518 (General) Correspondence, 1942, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 111)
      - C.S. Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Chartering, October 19, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to George Harris, January 3, 1945; 2.
  - Local 519 (Small Arms)
    - Local 519 (Small Arms) Incoming Correspondence, December 4, 1942 - May 10, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 112)
      - Julius Emspak to Jean Leslie Regarding Bonding, December 4, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Reg. Blackwell Regarding Bonding, July 16, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Alice Nelson Regarding Bonding, November 22, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Nelson Regarding Bonding, November 29, 1943; 4.
      - Edward Matthews to A.E. Sculthrop Regarding Automatic Control Plan, May 10, 1944; 5.
    - Local 519 (Small Arms) Outgoing Correspondence, May 10, 1941 - November 27, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 113)
      - R. Blackwell to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 24, 1943; 1.
      - Blackwell to Emspak Regarding Bonding, July 13, 1943; 2.
      - Blackwell to Emspak Regarding New Secretary, July 30, 1943; 3.
      - Alice Nelson to Emspak Regarding Bonding, November 27, 1943; 4.
      - A. Sculthorp to Ed Matthews Regarding Labor Briefs, May 10, 1941; 5.
    - Local 519 (Small Arms) Correspondence, 1942, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 114)
      - Julius Emspak to George Harris Regarding Organization, December 4, 1942; 1.
      - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 22, 1944; 2.
  - Local 519 (Ferranti)
    - Local 519 (Ferranti) Officers Lists, December 17, 1948 - April 1950 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Local 519 (Ferranti) Correspondence Regarding Draftmen Organization, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 116)
      - C.S. Jackson to Julius Emspak, December 17, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to Jackson, December 17, 1948; 2-3.
      - George Harris to Emspak, January 6, 1949; 4.
      - Ross Russell to Emspak, January 17, 1949; 5.
      - Emspak to C.S. Jackson, January 20, 1949; 6.
  - Local 520
    - Local 520 Officers Lists, October 25, 1942 - August 28, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Local 520 Incoming Correspondence, December 1942 - July 1954 (Box 6, Folder 118)
      - Paul Dunman to S.L. Farkas Regarding Contract, May 3, 1951; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Isaac Baker Regarding Bonding, December 17, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Baker Regarding Charter, March 3, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Ross MacLeod Regarding Bonding, March 9, 1949; 4.
      - Emspak to Les Nagy Regarding Check, November 19, 1951; 5.
      - L.W. Heironimus to Farkas Regarding Support of Curtis Refrigerator Workers, May 3, 1951; 6.
      - James Matles to Dunman Regarding Support Request, April 30, 1951; 7.
      - Matles to Farkas Regarding Work Stoppage, April 30, 1951; 8.
      - Secretary of Matles to Women in Aerovox, July 22, 1954; 9.
      - Matles to Ethel Knight Regarding Negotiations, July 27, 1954; 10.
      - Edward Matthews to Lyle Morrison Regarding Strike Support, February 8, 1946; 11.
    - Local 520 Outgoing Correspondence, 1950 - 1954 (Box 6, Folder 119)
      - S.L. Farkas to James Matles Regarding Negotiations, April 27, 1951; 1.
      - Farkas to George Harris Regarding Expenses, November 7, 1951; 2.
      - Lyle Morrison to Ed Matthews Regarding Membership Meeting, January 17, 1950; 3.
      - Women of Aerovox to James Matles Regarding Contract, July 16, 1954; 4.
      - F. Seymour to A. Fitzgerald Regarding Anti-Unionist, November 17, 1951; 5.
    - Local 520 Financial Accounts Report, November 5, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Local 520 Ontario Labor Relations Board Correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 121)
      - J.P. Nicol to UE, January 31, 1945; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Nicol, February 2, 1945; 2.
      - D.W. Mather to UE, November 17, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Mather, November 19, 1945; 4.
      - Mather to UE, November 27, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Mather, November 29, 1945; 6.
      - Mather to UE, February 19, 1946; 7.
      - Emspak to Mather, February 25, 1946; 8.
      - Mather to UE, June 1, 1946; 9.
      - Emspak to Mather, June 3, 1946; 10.
      - Mather to UE, November 30, 1946; 11.
      - Emspak to Mather, December 2, 1946; 12.
      - Mather to UE, February 14, 1947; 13.
      - Emspak to Mather, February 17, 1947; 14.
      - Mather to UE, February 21, 1947; 15.
    - Local 520 Correspondence, 1942 - 1953 (Box 6, Folder 122)
      - Julius Emspak to George Harris Regarding Organization, November 9, 1942; 1.
      - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 11, 1947; 2.
      - Nicholas Tomassetti to Harris, July 17, 1953; 3.
  - Local 521
    - Officers Lists, January 18, 1945 - September 22, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Local 521 Incoming Correspondence, 1942 - 1947 (Box 6, Folder 124)
      - Julius Emspak to A. Bissonette Regarding Waiver, June 27, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to William McIntyre Regarding Bonding, Dec 18, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Alex Welch Regarding Supplies, February 26, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Welch Regarding Supplies, March 31, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Stella Beber Regarding International Constitution, December 4, 1947; 5.
    - Local 521 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943 - 1947 (Box 6, Folder 125)
      - Stella Beber Letter Regarding Copy of Constitution, November 20, 1947; 1.
      - A. Bissonette to Julius Emspak Regarding Waiver Request, June 21, 1945; 2.
      - Ellis Blair to Emspak Regarding Bonding, January 4, 1949; 3.
      - Regina Bonneville to Emspak Regarding Supplies, September 4, 1944; 4.
      - W.R. Cambers Letter Regarding Supplies, September 6, 1944; 5.
      - Cambers to Emspak Regarding Supplies, no date; 6.
      - Alex Welch to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, February 22, 1943; 7.
      - Welch to Emspak Regarding Delinquency Notice, March 25, 1943; 8.
    - Local 521 Press Release Regarding Canada Wire and Cable Strike, December 15, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Local 522
    - Local 522 Officers Lists, February 21, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Local 522 Incoming Correspondence, 1943 - 1949 (Box 6, Folder 128)
      - Julius Emspak to Robert Ward Regarding Charter, January 6, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Allen Balson Regarding Bonding, January 6, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to W. Robb Regarding Union Organization, March 3, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Harold Bullock Regarding Officers, May 19, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Jack Hall Regarding Supplies, March 6, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Bullock Regarding Waiver, June 27, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Ellis Blair Regarding Fee, January 6, 1949; 7.
      - Emspak to Douglas Tyner Regarding Bonding, January 20, 1949; 8
    - Local 522 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943 - 1950 (Box 6, Folder 129)
      - Harold Bullock to Julius Emspak Regarding Election, May 20, 1943; 1.
      - Bullock to Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 21, 1943; 2.
      - Bullock to Emspak Regarding Strike, June 25, 1946; 3.
      - Bullock to Emspak Regarding Strike, Ferbuary 20, 1946; 4.
      - Douglas Tyner ot Emspak Regarding Bonding, January 10, 1949; 5.
      - Tyner to Emspak Regarding Bill, April 28, 1950; 6.
  - Local 523
    - Local 523 Officers Lists, March 8, 1942 - July 7, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Local 523 Incoming Correspondence, 1943 - 1950 (Box 6, Folder 131)
      - Fred d'Avila to Michael Bosnich Regarding Supplies, August 11, 1949; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to M. Hunka Regarding Union Composition, March 3, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Archie Hamilton Regarding Bonding, November 9, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to C.R. Sullivan Regarding Armed Forces Lists, January 14, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Sullivan Regarding Supplies, May 8, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Sullivan Regarding Strike Vote, May 14, 1946; 6.
      - Emspak to M. Bosnich Regarding Supplies, September 4, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak to Bosnich Regarding Bail, December 30, 1947; 8.
      - Emspak to Bosnich Regarding Audit, January 21, 1948; 9.
      - Secretary of James Matles to Bosnich, February 15, 1950; 10.
    - Local 523 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1954 (Box 6, Folder 132)
      - Michael Bosnich to Julius Emspak Regarding Meeting, December 23, 1947; 1.
      - Bosnich to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 9, 1948; 2.
      - Bosnich to Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 3, 1947; 3.
      - Bosnich to James Matles, February 9, 1950; 4.
      - Thomas Curran to Emspak Regarding Amendment Approval, November 9, 1949; 5.
      - Charles Enright Letter Regarding Meeting, January 31, 1950; 6.
      - J. Henderson to UE News Editor Regarding Print Permit, April 21, 1954; 7.
      - Emoma Meagher Letter Regarding Message Relay, February 14, 1950; 8.
      - P. Pawliuk to Emspak Regarding Charter, April 27, 1943; 9.
      - Pawliuk to Emspak Regarding Convention, July 16, 1943; 10.
      - C.R. Sullivan to Emspak Regarding Officers List, March 8, 1943; 11.
      - Sullivan to Emspak Regarding Employees List, January 7, 1944; 12.
      - Sullivan to Emspak Regarding Address Change, January 25, 1944; 13.
      - Sullivan to Emspak Regarding Srike, May 13, 1946; 14.
    - Local 523 Per Capita, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 133)
      - Julius Emspak to George Harris Regarding Per Capita, May 31, 1944; 1.
      - Harris to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, June 7, 1944; 2.
    - Local 523 Ontario Labor Relations Board, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 134)
      - J.P. Nicol to UE, February 6, 1945; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Nicol, February 16, 1945; 2.
      - D.W. Mather to UE, March 8, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak to Mather, March 11, 1946; 4.
    - Local 523 Ladies Auxiliary, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 135)
      - Julius Emspak to George Harris, November 11, 1945; 1.
      - Harris to Emspak, December 15, 1945; 2.
    - Local 523 Bonding, 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 136)
      - C.R. Sullivan to Julius Emspak, July 3, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Sullivan, July 10, 1945; 2.
      - Bob Ward to Emspak, July 2, 1947; 3.
    - Local 523 Carbon Council, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 137)
      - Charles Enright to Joseph Vejlupek, January 31, 1950; 1.
      - James Matles to Vejlupek, February 18, 1950; 2.
      - Matles to Herbert Hirchberg, February 15, 1950; 3.
    - Local 523 Correspondence, C.S. Jackson to James Matles Regarding Contracts, April 30, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 138)